http://www.docubank.com/index.cfm?event=info.privacy

Healthcare Card
College Card
Kids Card
Special NeedsAdults (S.N.A.P.)
Last updated 1/15/2014
DocuBank® is a service of Advance Choice, Inc. Advance Choice, Inc. is committed to the privacy of the personal information of its subscribers and customers. This privacy statement explains the data collection and use practices of Advance Choice through its DocuBank service. The statement does not apply to any other products or services that Advance Choice may develop.
By using the DocuBank service, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Personal Information and Document Collection
DocuBank stores your advance medical directive(s) (e.g. living will, durable power of attorney for health care, HIPAA, and/or anatomical gift designation, etc.) and related personal information. DocuBank also stores contact information of your emergency contacts and a primary physician so that they can be reached quickly by medical personnel in the event of an emergency, along with other user-defined optional information.
The minimal personal information collected by DocuBank upon registration, including name, address, phone number, email address, and date of birth, is collected for identification and billing purposes. Information beyond your name, address and phone number is optional.
DocuBank will not sell (other than in a transaction involving the sale of substantially all of Advance Choice, Inc.), loan, or rent, the information it stores for its members. The relevant documents and information are released only to those requesting it who are in possession of both the member number and PIN or access code found on your DocuBank Emergency Access Card.
Advance Choice contracts with several service providers for the purpose of processing memberships and maintaining the DocuBank information. These organizations are given access to the information collected by Advance Choice for the limited purpose of conducting their services. Each organization that is given access to the information must agree, in writing, to be bound by the privacy statement and privacy standards employed by Advance Choice.
Advance Choice strictly protects the security of the information you provide. Personal information that we collect is stored in a password-protected computer databases on servers with limited access. We carefully protect this information from loss, misuse, and other unauthorized disclosure, alteration or destruction.
The DocuBank website does not store any personally identifiable information about visitors to our site. DocuBank uses information only in aggregate form to track the total number of visitors to our site. When DocuBank members visit the Member Services portion of our website to update or renew membership information, the website uses a technology called "non-persistent cookies". A non-persistent cookie is a token that a server gives to your browser when you access a website or a section of a website. Our server uses a non-persistent cookie when you are updating or renewing your membership information to keep you from having to enter your password more than once during your visit to our site. This cookie is deleted once you leave our website.
An individual who is obtaining the advance directives of a DocuBank member from the website is required to provide identifying information. This information enables DocuBank to follow-up with the requestor regarding the quality of the retrieval service.
As a convenience to our visitors, DocuBank's website currently contains links to a number of sites that we believe may offer useful information. The privacy policies and procedures described here do not apply to those sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their data collection and distribution policies.
Information Retrieval
Your advance directives, emergency contact information and any other member-provided emergency information are available for retrieval via fax and the DocuBank website. To receive these documents and information, the requestor must be in possession of your member number and PIN (or access code),, both of which are found on your DocuBank Emergency Access Card. The documents and information will be supplied when both numbers are provided.
Upon enrollment, a member authorizes DocuBank to release their advance directives and related information to any person or entity in possession of both the member number and PIN (or access code). The Emergency Access Card also contains a signature space for member authorization. Additionally, DocuBank holds that any individual carrying their Emergency Access Card with them or on their person has also consented to and expects the retrieval of this information using the Emergency Access Card. By providing a fax number for the member's physician, the member grants DocuBank permission to fax an enrollment notification to this fax number to obtain the directives and related information stored by DocuBank.
Updating Information and Membership Renewal
You can renew your membership and/or update your personal and emergency contact information by: writing to DocuBank at P.O. Box 325 Narberth, PA 19072; calling a customer service representative at 1-866-DOCUBANK; or visiting our website, www.docubank.com. On the website, your member information can be viewed and/or changed only by an individual who is in possession of the member number, PIN (or access code) and a personal password. If you renew your membership via our website, your credit card information is processed via a certified secure authority.
DocuBank members must notify DocuBank promptly of changes in any of their stored information, and also of the revocation or replacement of their document(s). Members understand that DocuBank is not responsible for the validity or accuracy of any information stored by DocuBank, including the health information that also appears on the card. By accepting the Emergency Access Card, the member has verified and confirmed the accuracy of all information on the card before carrying it.
If a member has chosen to revoke or replace their advance directives, it is the member's responsibility to notify DocuBank promptly. You may view and print your advance directives from the DocuBank website; however, these documents cannot be edited or changed online. If you wish to add or make changes to your advance directive documents or to any of your documents stored with DocuBank, you must create a new version of the document(s), (you may wish to consult your attorney who prepared them for you) and submit these new documents to DocuBank Replacement Dept. P.O. Box 325 Narberth, PA 19072. Mark these documents as "additions" or "replacements" and include your DocuBank member number.
Loss of Card
If your DocuBank Emergency Card is lost or stolen, we will replace your card free of charge. At your request, we will issue a new PIN (or access code) so your documents cannot be accessed with your previous card.
Cancellation
You may cancel membership in DocuBank at any time by written request.  Prorated refunds will only be issued for members who are deceased.  Refunds for deceased members will be paid to the surviving spouse of the member or The Estate of the deceased member.
If you cancel your membership and wish to have your physical documents returned to you, there is a $25 physical document retrieval fee per member.  Disabling and or deleting your electronic documents so they are inaccessible via our service is free.
Disclosure Required by Law
Advance Choice may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on Advance Choice; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Advance Choice; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the DocuBank service, or the public.
Updates to Privacy Statement
We may occasionally update this Privacy Statement. When we do, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of the Privacy Statement. For material changes to this Privacy Statement we will notify you either by placing a prominent notice on the home page of our web site or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Statement to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the DocuBank service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Statement and any updates.
Site Directory
Home
Member Services
About DocuBank
How to Join
Attorneys
Financial Advisors
LGBT Community
DocuBank is a registered trademark of Advance Choice, Inc.
